you can put it here for now
I have to get out with my car
it has to cool down
Well, it's just that long stretch where you drive over that ridge
I was there when you called
There are cows on the left and then on the right a very large house with the roof off.
Just say...
Yes, but everywhere are cows and everywhere the roofs are off
yea that's true
ahh that one is good! how is it called again?
Gelderse rook worst.
This Old Rotterdam and this a Stolwijkse
I brought that one too, Old Rotterdam
No, yea exactly the same.
Yes, it's really nice.
I got it too, from Albert Heijn
It's the same.
You slept well, Cees?
Yes.
Did anything bite yet?
it's tight..?
yea i need a screwdriver
not... act normal
dad always does that as well
Yes..!
hahaha, like your eyes are closed
Always.
here you find them like hair on a dog
the small ones fall off
I think I'll cut some branches off, because it is better for a plum to be pruned in the summer.
What you do in winter, you will suffer more from silver leaf disease
And silver leaf is a disease which really damages it
You often get that infection earlier in the winter than in the summer.
I sleep like a princess, you know.
stop! no a bit further...
Cees will be surprised...
it will be all cleaned out
21:15, 21:30 back..?
I think more like 10 o'clock
I'll send a message
You'll probably see us standing there, Dad.
I believe the binoculars are there
Okay.
I will try
Bye!
Have a good journey.
I have self-timer on this one
I live for the breaks
Yeah.
It's all about the breaks
I think you're totally right.
Actually, I'm using your phrase this phrase with other people.
oh when you're not with me, it you make it your thing?
Yes. haha!
No, I say that it's your phrase.
I say: my love says that...
I told them.
That's good.
I'm fair
That's how I like it
"My biggest inspiration always says"
"That's how I like it, honey"
Oh, that smells so good
Dad, this is an Italian treat
Yea Cees, wait...
Yea yea. Sit!
Delicious!
with raw ham?
amazing, thanks!
Yes it really is a golden combination
Faithful Father, bless this meal we will be enjoying, that Siebren has prepared for us,
that we may rejoice in the wonders of Your Creation. You be thanked, praised, and worshipped.
Bless us for the remainder of this day and evening. We pray this, for and with each other, in Jesus' name, Amen.
Eat well!
G•••...
It's going well, guys..!
Binoculars?
This is Moon.
Moon?
Moon and Sun.
ah, Moon and Sun.
Because they're totally different.
One is brown and one is black and white.
Okay.
it has to move outside
No, that way...
that corner needs to align
It's one of my first jobs building the battery box
but soon enough... it was I wasn't built very well. I had to learn a lot
I wasn't able to insulate it which is important for batteries, the kind of batteries that I have now.
They need to be warm enough in winter, so taking it down because it has no purpose anymore
Yeah I've been cleaning up a lot this week.
Family was here.
They were here the whole week
It's always the same, we're always working hard here. And we're just spending most of our time here.
Not visiting much. Usually when you go on holiday you visit a lot of places, but we're...
It kind of means we have enough here. It's such a beautiful place to spend time together
You know, we have a lot of space here. At the outdoor kitchen, sometimes we're eating there, or here
We were sleeping in the workshop for the first time.
My dad is sleeping in the cabin and the rest is camping.
My brother has his own van.
Yeah, it's just really nice to spend time here in summer together. outside most of the time, working,
My dad always cuts the grass
So it looks already neat, because it was growing very high.
Spent a lot of time chipping wood, actually, because there were big piles of...
cut down birches over the years, so that was a lot of work.
We've got a big pile of mulch up there now
Yeah, this was really great.
We did a hike to the mountain, it was quite epic.
My dad couldn't come, because he can't hike up that steep.
It's quite a steep hike
up to 2100m (6890ft)
but yeah, it's always beautiful up there.
Didn't do that much work on the solar panels.
We prepared everything, the footings are finished, everything is stained, things are ready to go.
I had to do a lot of work here to dig in cables, organize things and wire it better.
So that's done.
Then next week I'll continue here and also at the workshop. I have to do a bit more on electricity
Another switch has arrived.
Yeah, small things.
But yeah, it's getting there.
Chicks are doing well.
They're becoming really beautiful birds. Like the black and white one is getting very spotted.
and the brown one as well but I think it will become more contrasting because it's the same breed
But a more brown version, so yeah, they're they're really pretty birds.